Guide to the Fulton Theater Records, 1934-1963 CTC.2000.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Fulton Theater Records
1934-1963
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Fulton Theater (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
CTC.2000.01
19.5 Linear Feet (43 boxes)
The Fulton Theater showed major motion pictures and operated in downtown Pittsburgh during the 1930's through the 1980's. The materials in this collection consist of operational and business files that contain financial reports, promotional materials, ledgers, correspondence, box office reports, and other materials related to the operation of the theater.
History
The Fulton Theater was located in Pittsburgh on the corner of Sixth Street and Fort Duquesne Boulevard from 1930's-1995. The theater was originally called the Gayety Theater. Built in 1903, it ran for thirty years as one of Pittsburgh's foremost stage and vaudeville houses. In the 1930's, the theater was renamed the Fulton and became a full time motion picture theater. The theater was purchased by the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust in 1990 and the Fulton was renovated and reopened in 1991. It was later renamed the Byham Theater through a naming right from the Byham family in 1995. The Fulton neon sign that had been displayed above the theater has been restored by the State Museum of Pennsylvania in Harrisburg and is installed there as part of a theater exhibit.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains the records of the Fulton Theater during the years of 1934-1963, but the majority of the collection dates from 1938-1951. The correspondence and motion picture files make up the majority of the collection. Films that are particularly well documented are Disney's Fantasia, Lawrence of Arabia, and The Best Years of Our Lives. Separate statistics for tickets sold and labor hours were kept during the film runs at the Fulton. Fastasia payroll information is located with the other payroll information in Series II and the statistics for the film ticket sales are kept with the box office statements in Series III. The collection has been arranged into the following series. Additional scope and content notes are available at the series level.
Arrangement
Series I. Correspondence, 1938-1951
Series II. Theater Operations, 1934-1951
Series III. Film Companies and Box Office records, 1930-1963
Series IV. Movie Files and Promotional Materials, 1944-1963
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was gifted to the University of Pittsburgh in two parts. In 1968, the first materials were given to the Archives Service Center. The Pittsburgh Cultural Trust donated more materials in May of 2000. The Archives Service Center transferred the Fulton records that were in their possession to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection in 2005.
Previous Citation
Fulton Theater Records, 1934-1963, CTC.2000.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Fulton Theater Records, 1934-1963, CTC.35, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Records of the Fulton Theater, 1962-1963, AIS 68:6a, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
Records of the Penn Theater, Pittsburgh, PA., 1927-1964, AIS.1968.06, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Fulton Theater Scrapbook, 1940-1943, Scrapbook Collection, Curtis Theatre Collection, University of Pittsburgh
Separated Material
Items related to the Penn Theater or other Shea chain theatres have been removed from this collection. The Penn materials have been added to the Records of the Penn Theater. The other Shea materials might be assembled into their own smaller collection.
Amusements -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theaters -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Byham Theater (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Social life and customs; Theater; Fulton Theater (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh Cultural Trust
- Correspondence, 1938-1951; I.
  Scope and Contents note
  The correspondence of the Fulton Theater records contains letters and memos that help illustrate its day to day activities, operations, and business dealings with local advertisers, national film companies, competing movie houses, and other entities. The series has been arrainged into three parts. The first part contains internal correspondence and the second features external correspondence. The final part contains mass memos which were called "form letters".
  Within each part of the internal and external correspondence, the letters are then arranged chronologically. The majority of the internal correspondence is between the theatre managers and other Shea-Chain Inc. or Jamestown Amusement Company personnel. In these documents many business subjects are discussed, such as: staffing decisions, budgeting, and advertising. The external correspondence is between the theatre management and the various film companies with which they conducted business. These letters discuss individual and package film contracts, revenue, and advertising rates. The form letters are usually addressed to "all managers" and contain information that was pertinent to all members of the company. For example, a form letter would be issued to inform managers about a method to advertise a particular film that has been successful in other towns, or, to remind managers of certain procedures that are not being followed.
  - Correspondence, 1938 - March, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
  - Correspondence, April, 1942 - 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence, January, 1944 - 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence, January, 1946 - June, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1-12)
  - Correspondence, July, 1948 - December, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence, 1950 - May, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1-13)
  - Best Years of Our Lives A-H, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Best Years of Our Lives I-Z, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Song of Bernadette, 1938-1945 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Telegrams, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Telegrams, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Telegrams, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Telegrams, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Telegrams, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Theater Operations, 1934-1951; II.
  This series contains employee payroll records and materials, newspaper clippings, tax information, bank books, candy sales reports, invoices and receipts, inspection certificates and licenses, materials related to the sale of war bonds and stamps at the theater, insurance information, and materials related to the Variety Club of Pittsburgh. The invoices and receipts are arranged in alphabetical order by name of company. Next is a small group of reports that show how much candy was sold on a weekly and monthly basis. Next is a series of bills, invoices, and purchase orders that are in an alphabetical arrangement by subject. They illustrate all of the expenses and maintenance necessary to keep the Fulton operating. In box 20 are examples of different types of 3-D glasses used for films at the Fulton. Also in box 20 are several unidentified photographic printing plates that may be images of managers of the Fulton and other Shea chain theaters. Managers of the Fulton and other theatres were members of the Pittsburgh Variety Club; box 20 contains account statements, correspondence, invoices, membership applications and lists dating between 1943 and 1948.
  - Payroll information, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 1-11)
  - Payroll information, 1946-1951 (Box 9, Folder 1-8)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Department of Labor and Industry (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Employee certificates, 1944-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Employer's tax returns, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Employment of minors, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Federal taxes, 1940-1949 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mercantile tax, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - National War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, no date-1950 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Payroll remittance vouchers (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Payroll stubs and envelopes (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Per capita tax returns, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - School tax, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - State Unemployment information, 1937-1951 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Taxable wages forms (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Timecards (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Withholding and Victory tax, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Withholding tax, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Bank books, 1934-1945 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Weekly record of bills,1943-1946, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - Deposit slips (Box 11, Item 3)
  - Monthly concession reports, 1940-1948 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Weekly candy stand reports, 1941-1946 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Advertising (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Art and art supplies (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Automobile repair (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bill posting (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Building / Construction (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Building materials (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Candy (Box 13, Folder 08-09)
  - Cleaning supplies (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Concessions (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Department stores (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Donations and Gratuities (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Electric and Lighting supplies (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Electrical work (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Engraving (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Exterminator (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Fire safety (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Flowers (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hotels (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Gun club (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Janitor's supplies (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Journal subscriptions (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Laundry and Tailoring (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Legal representation (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Lumber (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Message service and Telegrams (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Moving and Hauling (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper advertising (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Post Gazette advertising (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburgh Press advertising (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - This Week in Pittsburgh advertising (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Office supplies and furniture (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Painting (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Phipps Properties-- electric, water, steam bills (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Photography (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Plumbing (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Printing (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Projector (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Radio advertising (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Refrigeration (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Security system (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Services rendered and miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sign and display work (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sound equipment (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Telephone (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Theatre Managers Association of Pittsburgh (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Tickets (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Typewriters (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Uniforms (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Upholstery (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Valances (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Manager's expense account, 1941-1949 (Box 16, Folder 1-9)
  - City of Pittsburgh license receipts (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Department of Public Safety correspondence (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Department of Public Safety licenses (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Health Inspection certificates (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Other inspection certificates (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Board of Censors (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sign Maintenance and Inspection Certificates (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - War bond information and account statements (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - War bond receipts, 1942-1945 (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
  - War stamps (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Employee insurance files, 1930-1948 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hospital Service Association, 1941-1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Insurance accident reports, 1937-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - London Guarantee and Accident Company Ltd., 1939 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - M.J. Callahan Insurance, 1941-1949 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Bonding and Insurance Company, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Insurance, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Traveler's Insurance Company, 1945-1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 3-D glasses (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Movie Theater related journals (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photographic printing plates (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Variety Club materials, 1943-1948 (Box 20, Folder 4-12)
- Film Companies and Box Office records, 1930-1963; III.
  This series contains the contracts and receipts from the motion picture studios, film time schedules, hourly ticket reports, examples of tickets and materials related to the tickets themselves, and the box office statements. These records are first arranged alphabetically by motion picture company and then by date. They contain receipts and contracts for the rentals of their films by the Fulton. The time schedules in this series document at exactly what times movies and their opening attractions started and finished for each showing on a particular day. The hourly ticket reports break-up the day by hour and list the amount sold in each price category. The box office statements that are included in this series are a daily record of a particular film title at the Fulton. They list the date, day of the week, title, how many matinee and evening tickets were sold, how many were adult tickets and how many were children. Also, on the statement is the weather and sometimes films that were playing at other theaters in the area.
  - Columbia Pictures, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Crown Film, 1941-1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - De Lux Labs, Inc, - "Football This Week" (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Film Classics Inc., 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Film Exchange, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - International Picture Distributing Company Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lux Film Distributing Company, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Monarch, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - MGM, 1941-1948 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - National Screen Service, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Paramount, 1942-1949 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Producer's Releasing Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - RKO, 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Release Charts, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Republic Pictures, 1942-1949 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
  - Select Attractions, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Short Subject Playoffs, 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 20th Century Fox, 1939-1944 (Box 21, Folder 19-21)
  - 20th Century Fox, 1945-1949 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Universal, 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3-7)
  - Universal, 1946-1950 (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
  - United Artists, 1940, 1942-1946 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Vitagraph / Warner Bros., 1941-1943 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Time schedules, 1938, 1942, 1945, 1947-1949 (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
  - Hourly ticket reports, 1934 - 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Hourly ticket reports, 1937 - 1939 (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Hourly ticket reports, 1940 - 1943 (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
  - Tickets (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ticket refunds (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Price lists (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Schedules (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Service charges (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Box Office statements, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Box Office statements, 1930 - 1933 (Box 29, Folder 2-6)
  - Box Office statements, 1934 -1937 (Box 30, Folder 1-5)
  - Box Office statements, 1938 - 1939 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Box Office statements, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - Box Office statements, Fantasia, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Box Office statements, Jan.-April, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Box Office statements, May, 1941 - 1942 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
  - Box Office statements, 1942 - 1943 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
  - Box Office statements, 1943 - 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1-5)
  - Box Office statements, 1962 - 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
- Movie Files and Promotional Materials, 1944-1963; IV.
  These files are arranged alphabetically by film title. These files represent most, but probably not all, of the films that were shown at the Fulton during the 1940's. They contain bills for advertisements in local newspapers, radio spots, etc. They also contain proof copies of the engraving advertisements that would appear in the newspapers. Box 43 contains press releases, synopsis, and other promotional materials for films that were featured at the Fulton.
  - Abandoned, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Abbot and Costello Meet Frankenstein, Universal, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Abbot and Costello Meet the Killers, Universal, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - All My Sons, Universal, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Angel and the Bad Man, Republic, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Anna and the King of Siam, 20th Century Fox, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Another Part of the Forest, Universal, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Apartment for Peggy, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Are You with It, Universal, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Belle Starr, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Belle Starr's Daughter, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - A Bell for Adono, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Best Years of Our Lives, MGM and RKO, 1947-1948 (Box 38, Folder 13-15)
  - Bill and Coo, Republic, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Bishop's Wife, RKO, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Black Gold, Monogram, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Blithe Spirit, United Artists, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Boomerang, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Brasher Boubloon, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Brute Force, Universal, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Calamity Jane and Samm Bass, Universal, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Canyon Passage, Universal, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Captain from Castille, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Christopher Columbus, Republic, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Climax, 20th Century Fox, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Cobra Woman, Universal, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Countess of Monte Cristo, Universal, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Criss Cross, Universal, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Cry of the City, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Daisy Kenyon, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Dakota, Republic, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Daltons Ride Again, Universal, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Dark Corner, 20th Century Fox, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Dark Mirror, Universal, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Dear Murderer and Maneater of Kumnam, Universal, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Deep Waters, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Diamond Horseshoe, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Diary of a Chambermaid, United Artists, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Doll Face, 20th Century Fox, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Dolly Sisters, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Dragonwyck, 20th Century Fox, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Earl Carroll's Sketchbook, Republic, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Earl Carroll's Vanities, Republic, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Egg and I, Universal, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Enchanted Forest, PRC, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Enchantment, RKO, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Fabulous Texan, Republic, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Father was a Fullback, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Fighting Kentuckian, Republic, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Fighting Man, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Flame, Republic, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Flame of the Barbary Coast, Republic, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - For the Love of Many, Universal, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Frisco Sal, Universal, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Fury at Furnace Creek, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Gallant Legion, Republic, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Gal Who Took West, Universal, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Great Expectations, Universal, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Hangover Square, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Homestretch, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - House on 92nd Street, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Imitation of Life and East Side of Heaven, Universal, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - In Old Sacramento, Republic, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Iron Curtain, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - I've Always Loved You, Republic, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - I Wonder Who's Kissing Her Now, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - John Dillinger, Monogram, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Keys of the Kingdom, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Kid from Brooklyn, RKO, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Kid from Cleveland, Republic, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Kiss of Death, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Lady in Ermine, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Lady on a Train, Universal, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Lawrence of Arabia, Columbia, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Lost Moment, Universal, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Ma and Pa Kettle, Universal, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Male War Bride, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Mark of Zorro, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Men in Her Diary, Universal, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Mexican Hayride, Universal, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Mexicana, Republic, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Mr. Emmanuel, United Artists, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Mr. Peabody and the Mermaid, Universal, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Moonrise, Republic, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Mother is a Freshman, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - My Darling Clementine, 20th Century Fox, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - My Pal Trigger and Rendezvous with Annie, Republic, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Ninotchka, MGM, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Oh, You Beautiful Doll, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Once More My Darling, Universal, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Outlaw, United Artists, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Panhandle, Monogram, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Pinocchio, Disney, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Plunderers, Republic, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Pride of the Yankees, RKO, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Rebecca, United Artists, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Red Canyon, Universal, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Red Menace, Republic, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Red Pony, Republic, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Ride the Pink Horse, Universal, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - River Lady, Universal, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Rosanna McCoy, RKO, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Runaround, Universal, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Sand, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Sands if Iwo Jima, Republic, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Saxon Charm, Universal, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Scarlet Street, Universal, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Scudda Ho, Scudda Hay!, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Secret Behind the Door, Universal, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Secret Life of Walter Mitty, RKO, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Shocking Miss Pilgrim, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Smart Woman, Monogram, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - So Goes My Love, Universal, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Something in the Wind, Universal, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Song is Born, RKO, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Song of Bernadette, 20th Century Fox, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - South Sea Sinner, Universal, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Stairway to Heaven, Universal, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Street with No Name, 20th Century Fox, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Sudan, Universal, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sunbonnet Sue, Monogram, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Suspect, Universal, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Suspense, Monogram, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Temptation, Universal, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - That Brennan Girl, Republic, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - That Night with You, Universal, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - That Wonderful Urge, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - That's the Spirit, Universal, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Thunderhead, 20th Century Fox, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Time of their Lives, Universal, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - This Love of Ours, Universal, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 19)